iebusiness.com 2018-01-11

# Privacy Policy

We appreciate any concerns you may have about the privacy and security of your personal information on the Web. We value your personal information as if it is our own. We want your experience on our site to be of value and importance to you as well as informative. We also want you to trust that we make every effort to protect your confidentiality. Personal information is requested in some areas of this site in order to enable us to provide you with the best customer experience possible. The amount and type of information received depends on how you use this site. Information may be stored and used in order to enhance your experience. Your use of ie-business.com implies your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. You also grant ie-business.com permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. 

The contents of the infusion e-business Web site are provided as general information only. In no event will ie-business or the contributors of information to this site be held liable for any action taken by you in reliance on such information or for any consequential, special or similar damages. The following discloses the practices of ie-business for protecting the privacy of visitors to the Web site: www.ie-business.com. 

Note: Visitors can access all sections of the Web site without providing any personal, identifying information. 

## Information We Collect

The only data we collect and store during normal Web site usage is typical Web server log data. Examples of this type of data are: the name of your Internet service provider, the site that referred you to us, any pages you request, the time and date of those requests, etc. From time to time, ie-business.com may conduct surveys, contests and sweepstakes via this site, email or other media. If you participate, we may collect your name, email address, mailing address and other personal information. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties. 

At times, we request personally identifiable information to provide site visitors with a service. This information, such as name, mailing/shipping address, email address, payment related information, and type of request, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the request to fulfill your needs. It is never provided or sold to any other company for that company's independent use. 

## Cookies and Other Computer Information

When you visit ie-business.com, you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of this cookie is to identify you when you visit the site so that we can enhance and customize your online experience. You can choose to browse on ie-business.com without cookies. However, without these identifier files you may not be able to take advantage of certain features of the Site. 

Each browser is different, so check your browser's "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to ie-business.com. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring Website, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to the site and will not sell or rent this information to any third parties. 

## How We Use Personal Information

We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to benefit the users of this site. This same information may be shared with third parties in order to provide these services or to analyze, store, or aggregate the information. It may also be shared with other third parties, working with us to improve our services or this website. 

### When and With Whom We Share Your Personal Information 

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer information and/or purchase history only with our agents, representatives, service providers and contractors for limited purposes, including but not limited to: fulfilling customer orders; offering certain products and services in connection with this site; communicating to clients; providing customer service; enhancing and improving client online experiences; administering or facilitating surveys, contests or sweepstakes; offering targeted marketing communications to users that opted-in to receive such communications; enabling access to our partners' Web sites; providing a personalized online experience; preventing fraud; and completing payment method processing. 

Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required to prevent harm or injury (such as product recalls, fraud, claims or other liability), or to comply with valid legal processes (subpoenas, warrants) as required by law. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We also contract with third parties to provide us with: data collection and reporting services regarding our clients' activities on the Site; tracking and measuring performance of our marketing efforts and your response to our marketing efforts; and the delivery of relevant marketing messages. These third parties may use cookies and Web beacons (1 x 1 pixels), and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on the Site. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, credit card number, etc.) will be received by or shared with these third parties. If you do not want your non-personal information used to serve ads to you, you can change the settings of your browser to reject cookies. Each browser is different, so check your browser's "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

## Links

This site contains links to other sites. These links are provided for your convenience and are not intended as an endorsement by ie-business of the entities operating these sites nor as a warranty of the information the sites contain. Infusion e-business is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other Web sites, and urges users to review the privacy policies of the individual sites. Visitors always can accept or reject any cookies from our Web sites by taking advantage of the related settings and tools on their own computers. 

## Security

The SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) is the most powerful encryption available on the Internet. This means that any information related to credit cards is encrypted when being sent to us, so no one else is able to read it. 

Having a secure server takes the risk out of credit card transactions. We also do all order processing on software that is separate from the Internet, so there is no danger of anyone gaining access to your order information. We do NOT keep credit card information on file. While we realize this reducing future ordering convenience, we feel that the safest way to protect credit card information is not to store it, but request it each time a purchase is made.   
Please note: that email is not encrypted and not considered a secure way to transmit credit card information. 

## Children

Users of all ages are welcome to visit ie-business.com and view its contents. However, supervision of children's activities on the Internet is the responsibility of parents or legal guardians to ensure that children do not release personal and/or purchasing information online without permission. 

We do not solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, email address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or legal guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law. 

## Voluntary Use of Contact Forms

Infusion e-business forms may request that visitors voluntarily provide personal information, including name, company/organization, city and state of residence, and telephone numbers. The contact information is only used to contact the visitor as requested. Infusion e-business does NOT distribute to third parties any information provided on infusion e-business forms. Infusion e-business will not disclose an individual's/employee's identifying information provided by voluntary use of a Contact Form, or specific use of the system to any individual, employer, or organization under any circumstances. Further, only a group of trained and authorized employees has access to information you volunteer via a Contact Form. All infusion e-business employees must abide by our Privacy Policy. Employees violating this Privacy Policy are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination. 

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

This Web site Privacy Policy is effective as of December 1, 2009. Periodically, it may be necessary to make modifications to this Policy. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notification. However, changes will not be applied retroactively and will not alter the management of previously collected information. If changes are made to this Policy, we will post the revised version on this Web site so you may want to periodically review this section for the most current version of our Privacy Policy. 

### Contacting ie-business Regarding This Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our site, or your dealings with our Web site, please contact: 

Web Site Manager  
infusion e-business  
ie-business.com  
902 S. Randall Road  
Suite C319  
St. Charles, IL  60174
